<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projects. on Hovio.us</title><link>/project/</link><description>Recent content in Projects. on Hovio.us</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Desktop RGB Lamp</title><link>/project/rgbdesklamp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/project/rgbdesklamp/</guid><description>Desktop RGB Lamp Building a simple project that will allow moving of a 180* servo via a potentometer and 1306 screen. About This project
Hardware Required Arduino Board Any arduino should work, using a Nano clone Servo Motor 0.96 OLED Used to show the current servo arm angle. Can be ommited and monitored using the serial monitor. I used an 0.96 SSD1306 display 64x128. 10k Potentometer Used for adjusting the angle of the servo hook-up wires Circuit Pin Description 25 SDA &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; OLED 26 SCL &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; OLED A0 Potentometer &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; OLED 9 Servo Pin Assembly INSERT PIC OF BOARD WITHOUT MODULES IN IT *OTHER PICS Potentometer Circuit Wire the potentiometer so that its two outer pins are connected to power (+5V) and ground, and its middle pin is connected to A0 on the board.</description></item><item><title>Servo Testing/Control Board</title><link>/project/srvotest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/project/srvotest/</guid><description>Building a simple project that will allow moving of a 180* servo via a potentometer and 1306 screen.
About This project serves the purpose of building a small servo control device. This device allows connection of a standard 180* rotation servo. The angle of the servois adjusted using the potentometer. The active angle of the servo is displayed on the connected screen
Hardware Required Arduino Board Any arduino should work, using a Nano clone Servo Motor 0.</description></item></channel></rss>